http://www.friarsclub.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us, and it is The Friars Club's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.
Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. The Friars Club may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and at The Friars Club's sole discretion.
THE FRIARS CLUB
57 East 55th Street
New York, New York 10022
Phone: 212-751-7272
Terms of Service
Privacy Policy
© Copyright 2015. Friars Club. All Rights Reserved.
The Friars Club Remembers Aretha Franklin
×
Friars Club Specialty Drinks
THE RUMPKIN
Pumpkin and Rum, a winning combination, like Reiner & rooks, Burns & Allen and Poehler & Fey. Raise a rocks glass with a lemon wedge on the rim to these dynamic and delicious duos. A drink even the 2,000-year-old man could enjoy.
2 oz. Pyrat Rum
1 oz. Cinnamon Syrup
1 oz. Fresh Apple Cider
1 Dash of Fresh Lemon Juice
RYE SENSE OF HUMOR
Whether being roasted, toasted, feted, or awarded, a Friar relies on his wry sense of humor. Our Rye Sense Of Humor relies on Rye, Cream Sherry, Fresh Apple Aider, and other fine ingredients. Top with three house-made Bourbon Cherries skewered like a Friars Club Roastee.
1 oz. Rye
2 oz. Cream Sherry
1 oz. Fresh Apple Cider
3-5 Dashes Orange Bitters
1 Dash Bourbon Cherry Juice
THE BOURBON LEGEND
Our new Bourbon Legend is like mixing Uncle Milte, Buddy Hackett, Phyllis Diller and Jerry Lewis all into one glass. Your entre into the world of old-fashioned fizz and showbiz. You’ll be the Toastmaster General every time with this Friars favorite.
1 oz. Rye
2 oz. Cream Sherry
1 oz. Fresh Apple Cider
3-5 Dashes Orange Bitters
1 Dash Bourbon Cherry Juice
WHAT A PEAR!
Laurel & Hardy, Abbott & Costello, Rowan & Martin… all classic comedy pairs. Think of them while sipping this classic pear-flavored drink. Poir Williams pear-flavored brandy combined with the finest ingredients for the straight man or quipster in all of us.
2 oz. Poire Williams
1.25 oz Fresh Lemon Juice
1 oz. Clove Syrup
1 Bar spoonful Pear Pureé
Drink names and descriptions courtesy of Friar Lisa Lampanelli
×
